<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Melio Consulting</title>
    <link>https://melio.ai/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Melio Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 13:00:34 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://melio.ai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker: Introdocktion</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/training/kubernetes/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:26:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/training/kubernetes/docker/</guid>
      <description>A hands-on workshop to the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular containerisation technology!
Attendees will learn about the fundamental building block that enables technologies such as Kubernetes. The hands-on portion of this workshop emphasises on how Docker can enhance software development workflows.
This workshop is best suited for attendees that have no experience with Docker but are familiar with software development (no pre-requisites on any specific programming language).
 Agenda This workshop introduces attendees to the basics of using Docker from the developer&amp;rsquo;s and operation&amp;rsquo;s perspective and consists of two segments: theory and hands-on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubeflow Workshop</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/training/kubeflow/kubeflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:26:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/training/kubeflow/kubeflow/</guid>
      <description>Kubeflow is a machine learning platform native to Kubernetes.
(Workshop outline coming soon!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Workshop: Fundamental</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/training/kubernetes/fundamental/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 23:35:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/training/kubernetes/fundamental/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Kubernetes basics including theory and a hands-on playground.
This workshop is best suited for attendees that have no experience with Kubernetes and would like some hands-on experience with a real Kubernetes cluster.
This workshop is structured for attendees who has no experience with Kubernetes. Some experience with containerisation technology is recommended. Ideally, the attendees should have completed Docker: Introdocktion.
 Agenda This workshop introduces attendees to the Kubernetes basics from a software development perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Workshop: Intermediate</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/training/kubernetes/intermediate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 22:14:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/training/kubernetes/intermediate/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to CNCF projects with Kubernetes.
This workshop is best suited for attendees who would like to know more about the power of Kubernetes beyond the default configurations. This workshop introduces several CNCF projects which are powerful additions to the Kubernetes cluster.
This workshop aims to showcase the usage of a Kubernetes cluster in a realistic and practical scenario. Hence this workshop is presented as a series of problems in a form of a laboratory that attendees can complete at their own pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Workshop: Advanced</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/training/kubernetes/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 23:37:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/training/kubernetes/advanced/</guid>
      <description>This workshop is geared towards teams that have implemented Kubernetes within their organisations and would like to further their Kubernetes journey by learning about the best practices around configuring a production-ready, enterprise-level Kubernetes cluster.
This workshop is only relevant to attendees that have Kubernetes currently deployed either in a development or production environment.
 Agenda This workshop is tailored to the attendees&amp;rsquo; current Kubernetes set up and hence the agenda will be different depending on the needs of the team/organisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ - July, 2021</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2021-07-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2021-07-28/</guid>
      <description>Transforming into a zero-bug super developer on Kubernetes Summary For our July meetup, we have Lepolesa Libete coming to explore a cool Kubernetes tool: DevSpace with us.
DevSpace helps developers build applications that run on Kubernetes. It brings the deployment environment (i.e. Kubernetes) closer to developers working on the application. This empowers developers to collaborate and discover issues early during development.
DevSpace lets you start the entire deployment workflow with a single command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ - April, 2021</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2021-04-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2021-04-14/</guid>
      <description>How to think Cloud Native for your next Data project? Summary We invited cloud-native specialist Harry Lee and data specialist Archana Arakkal to chat about how the two ecosystems are growing to serve the community. And how you, as a practitioner, can start thinking cloud-native to improve your efficiency!
Here&amp;rsquo;s is the timestamped breakdown of the items discussed:
 5:10: What are some examples of data projects in public, hybrid and multi-cloud environments?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ - November, 2020</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-11-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-11-25/</guid>
      <description>If it ain&amp;rsquo;t broke, rewrite it! - Inject innovation in restrictive environments Summary How do you rewrite code while keeping the business running? Jose Pita has taken us through his team&amp;rsquo;s cloud native journey and shared his team&amp;rsquo;s experiences in overcoming technical as well as business challenges.
In this session, Jose covered:
  Standard Bank Alchemy team&amp;rsquo;s cloud native journey  How to build trust and speak to business  How to nurture a long lasting team culture  How to build a team and not a product  Session Recording   References  Slides (PPT)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ - September, 2020</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-09-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-09-23/</guid>
      <description>Using Google Anthos to unlock cloud-native hybridization awesomeness Summary Google Anthos has come a long way since its GA announcement more than a year ago. Anthos is a combination of many services under the hood - all revolving around easing the deployment of Kubernetes anywhere and everywhere.
Julian has taken us through how a hypothetical SaaS company leverages Anthos to deliver their products to their customers.
In this session, Julian covered:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ - July, 2020</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-07-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-07-29/</guid>
      <description>Multi-cluster Kubernetes, the easy way [with Rancher] Summary We had the pleasure of hosting Tom Otomanski at our July CNCJ meetup last week. Tom showcased how Rancher enables effortless management of multiple Kubernetes clusters through a single interface.
In this session, Tom covered:
  Creating a Kubernetes cluster on AWS through Rancher  Managing Kubernetes cluster with common operations through Rancher  Showcased all Kubernetes configurations in the Rancher GUI  Session Recording   References  Slides (PDF) Rancher Server Documentation Rancher Blog Kubernetes Master Class Rancher Academy Rancher Labs YouTube Rancher Users Slack  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ - June, 2020</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-06-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-06-29/</guid>
      <description>[Kubernetes] A demo of Rancher&amp;rsquo;s RKE Summary Bradley Cloete gave us a glimpse into the power and simplicity of Rancher&amp;rsquo;s RKE. RKE&amp;rsquo;s easy Kubernetes life cycle management is a breeze for novice and experts alike. Bradley showed us how Kubernetes&amp;rsquo; day 2 operations (cluster backup/restore/scale) can be straightforward with RKE.
Session Recording   References  Rancher Academy: Certified Rancher Operator: Level 1  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ - May, 2020</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-05-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-05-26/</guid>
      <description>[Kubernetes] Embracing Failure: Lessons learned from 50 post-mortems Summary In this session, Moshe&amp;rsquo;s covered his anecdotal lessons learned on deploying Kubernetes:
 ⛔ Some of the most common failure modes of Kubernetes clusters ⭐ Best practices you can apply to mitigate these failure modes 👨‍💻 A live demo simulating failure and then applying policies to prevent it  Session Recording   Slides Google Docs: Embracing failure - Lessons learned from 50 post-mortems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ - Feb, 2020</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-02-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-02-13/</guid>
      <description>Webinar - Kubernetes Fundamentals Summary We enjoyed how Roger simplifies the complex jargons and concepts into simple analogies. The demo on local deployment of a Kubernetes cluster was easy-to-follow and comprehensive.
Here is a summary on one of the Q&amp;amp;A&amp;rsquo;s:
 ❓ What is the landscape of Kubernetes in South Africa enterprise? Are they using it in production or are still hesitant? 💬 Enterprise are paying a conscious effort in developing the competency in cloud-native technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Scientist</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/careers/data-scientist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/careers/data-scientist/</guid>
      <description>Melio is seeking a passionate Data Scientist to join our expanding team:
 Level: Junior or Intermediate Position: Full time Salary: Based on technical experience Location: South Africa (Remote)   As a fast-paced start-up, our day-to-day is never the same. We look for candidates who love to take up new challenges and have the flexibility to go above-and-beyond the call of duty.
That being said, this specific role is for a team member to work in the Machine Learning AI team as a Data Scientit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Engineer</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/careers/dev-ops-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/careers/dev-ops-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Melio is seeking a passionate DevOps Engineer to join our expanding team:
 Level: Intermediate Position: Full time Salary: Negotiable based on technical experience Location: South Africa (Remote)  Minimum 1 year of experience working with Kubernetes (essential)
Have software (fullstack) development experience
 As a fast-paced start-up, our day-to-day is never the same. We look for candidates who love to take up new challenges and have the flexibility to go above-and-beyond the call of duty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fullstack Engineer</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/careers/fullstack-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/careers/fullstack-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Melio is seeking a passionate Fullstack Engineer to join our expanding team:
 Level: Intermediate - Senior Position: Full time Salary: Negotiable based on technical experience Location: South Africa (Remote)  Minimum 2 years of experience working with as a fullstack engineer.
Backend experience preferrably with Python but Go and Java experience are fine. Frontend with React / Vue JS.
 As a fast-paced start-up, our day-to-day is never the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving data scientist productivity by 80%</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-1/</guid>
      <description>Hello   with the implementation of an end-to-end machine learning platform  “ Fluid has simplified out model building and deployment process, and allowed for integration across our various platforms ”   Rainer Schilder - Lead Data Scientist   Case Study  Industry
 Technology
  Company Size
 51 - 200 employees
  Project
 Length 7 months
  Team Size</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Azure Machine Learning to improve billing accuracy and consistency</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-5/</guid>
      <description>Hello   with the implementation of an end-to-end machine learning platform  -- “ This is the beginning of how we will change the way we work with data ”   GM - Pharmacy   Case Study  Industry
 Health Care
  Company Size
 10,001+ employees
    Problem Space  Predictive Analytics
Azure Insights
Machine Learning
Billing
   Technology Used  Python</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Engineer</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/careers/machine-learning-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/careers/machine-learning-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Melio is seeking a passionate Machine Learning Engineer to join our expanding team:
 Level: Junior or Intermediate Position: Full time Salary: Based on technical experience Location: South Africa (Remote)   As a fast-paced start-up, our day-to-day is never the same. We look for candidates who love to take up new challenges and have the flexibility to go above-and-beyond the call of duty.
That being said, this specific role is for a team member to work in the Machine Learning AI team as a Machine Learning Engineer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimising debt collection efforts for over 1 million cases</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-4/</guid>
      <description>Hello   with the implementation of a cloud-based debt prioritisation solution  “ The solution helped us to work the right cases first and reduce the time taken to work a case by more than 50% ”   Head of Debtors Shared Services - Quote is paraphrased   Case Study  Industry
 Health Care
  Company Size
 10,001+ employees
    Problem Space  Predictive Analytics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail and business banking rolling forecast</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-2/</guid>
      <description>Hello   for the budgeting process with what-if analysis scenario planning  “ What-if analysis lets my team help our business partners achieve their financial goals ”   Head of Retail Banking - Quote is paraphrased   Case Study  Industry
 Banking
  Company Size
 10,000+ employees
    Problem Space  Predictive Analytics
Insights Automation
Data Science
   Technology Used  Python</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time savings for finance team on monthly financial reporting automation</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/use-cases/use-case-3/</guid>
      <description>Hello   with Microsoft AX Dynamics  “ The solution saves me a lot of time every month and we look forward to expand it to rest of the business ”   Finance Manager - Quote is paraphrased   Case Study  Industry
 Manufacturing
  Company Size
 501 - 1,000 employees
    Problem Space  Digitisation
AWS Automation
Data Engineering</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/training/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 17:19:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/training/pricing/</guid>
      <description>.background { padding: 0 25px 25px; position: relative; width: 100%; } .background::after { content: &#39;&#39;; background: #f7964c; background: -moz-linear-gradient(top, #f7964c 0%, #e97d29 100%); background: -webkit-linear-gradient(top, #f7964c 0%,#e97d29 100%); background: linear-gradient(to bottom, #f7964c 0%,#e97d29 100%); filter: progid:DXImageTransform.Microsoft.gradient( startColorstr=&#39;#f7964c&#39;, endColorstr=&#39;#e97d29&#39;,GradientType=0 ); height: 350px; left: 0; position: absolute; top: 0; width: 100%; z-index: 1; } @media (min-width: 1300px) { .background { padding: 0 0 25px; } } .container { margin: 0 auto; padding: 50px 0 0; max-width: 960px; width: 100%; } .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetups</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/meetups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/meetups/</guid>
      <description>.card { box-shadow: 0 4px 8px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.2); transition: 0.3s; border-radius: 5px; margin: auto; width: 75%; } .card:hover { box-shadow: 0 8px 16px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.2); } .container { padding: 10px; width: inherit; } .attend { border: none; outline: 0; display: inline-block; padding: 8px; color: white; background-color: #e97d29; text-align: center; cursor: pointer; font-size: 18px; margin: 10px 0px; }  Cloud Native Computing Johannesburg (CNCJ) Wed, 28 July, 6:00PM Transforming into a zero-bug super developer on Kubernetes  Online Webinar   DevSpace helps developers build applications that run on Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Methodology</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/how/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/how/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/privacy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/use-cases-html/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/use-cases-html/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
