<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kubernetes Workshop Series on Melio Consulting</title>
    <link>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kubernetes Workshop Series on Melio Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 22:09:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker: Introdocktion</title>
      <link>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:26:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/docker/</guid>
      <description>A hands-on workshop to the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular containerisation technology!
Attendees will learn about the fundamental building block that enables technologies such as Kubernetes. The hands-on portion of this workshop emphasises on how Docker can enhance software development workflows.
This workshop is best suited for attendees that have no experience with Docker but are familiar with software development (no pre-requisites on any specific programming language).
 Agenda This workshop introduces attendees to the basics of using Docker from the developer&amp;rsquo;s and operation&amp;rsquo;s perspective and consists of two segments: theory and hands-on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Workshop: Fundamental</title>
      <link>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/fundamental/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 23:35:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/fundamental/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Kubernetes basics including theory and a hands-on playground.
This workshop is best suited for attendees that have no experience with Kubernetes and would like some hands-on experience with a real Kubernetes cluster.
This workshop is structured for attendees who has no experience with Kubernetes. Some experience with containerisation technology is recommended. Ideally, the candidate should have completed Docker: Introdocktion.
 Agenda This workshop introduces attendees to the Kubernetes basics from a software development perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Workshop: Intermediate</title>
      <link>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/intermediate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 22:14:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/intermediate/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to CNCF projects with Kubernetes.
This workshop is best suited for attendees who would like to know more about the power of Kubernetes beyond the default configurations. This workshop introduces several CNCF projects which are powerful additions to the Kubernetes cluster.
This workshop aims to showcase the usage of a Kubernetes cluster in a realistic and practical scenario. Hence this workshop is presented as a series of problems in a form of a laboratory that attendees can complete at their own pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Workshop: Advanced</title>
      <link>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 23:37:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.co.za/training/kubernetes/advanced/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to best practices, automation (CI/CD), security and auditing in Kubernetes.
(Workshop outline coming soon!)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>