<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Melio Consulting</title>
    <link>https://melio.ai/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Melio Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://melio.ai/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CNCJ Meetups</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/meetups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/meetups/</guid>
      <description>Cloud Native Computing Johannesburg (CNCJ) 2023 An Introduction to Kubeflow, the MLOps Platform on Kubernetes Fri, 29 September, 6:00PM Online Webinar CNCF event link Optimizing Network Costs in Kubernetes Wed, 26 July, 6:00PM Online Webinar CNCF event link Synthetic Testing with Canary Checker Thu, 25 May, 6:00PM Online Webinar CNCF event link 2022 Scaling Kubernetes with Karpenter: Advanced Scheduling with Pod Affinity Thu, 25 August, 6:00PM Online Webinar CNCF event link Cloud-native machine learning: Kubeflow success stories Wed, 29 June, 6:00PM Online Panel Discussion meetup event link External Secrets Operator: A Cloud Native way to manage your secrets Wed, 25 May, 6:00PM Online Webinar CNCF event link 2021 Transforming into a zero-bug super developer on Kubernetes Wed, 28 July, 6:00PM Online Webinar meetup event link How to think Cloud Native for your next Data project?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://melio.ai/events/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://melio.ai/events/events/</guid>
      <description>2024 Unlock the Power of Gen AI for Fintech with AWS 3 April 2024
Host: AWS
Webinar Recordings
Over 70% of businesses see GenAI as a growth opportunity but view it as a confusing and risky gamble. We&amp;rsquo;ve spoken to numerous businesses and developers, and the sentiment is clear—it feels overwhelming. In this webinar, you will learn:
Overview of AWS Services in Gen AI High Impact Gen AI Use Cases in FinTech Gen AI Use Case Considerations Transforming Businesses using AI 27 March 2024</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
