<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resources :: Melio Consulting</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/index.html</link><description>A collection of resources from our events.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://melio.ai/events/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CNCJ - April, 2025</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2025-04-09/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2025-04-09/index.html</guid><description>Kubernetes at Scale - Why Enterprises Bet Big on Cloud Native Summary Kubernetes is changing the way enterprises develop, scale, and manage their applications in the cloud. It’s no longer just a trend, it’s the backbone of modern IT strategies. But how exactly is it making an impact on enterprises? We’d love for you to join us as we dive into this game-changing technology and hear from industry experts!
We’re excited to partner with BSG, a proudly South African consulting and technology company that has been a driving force in the tech industry, providing solutions to optimise business performance. With expertise in cloud solutions, data-driven insights, and digital transformation, BSG helps businesses tackle complex challenges, making them the ideal partner for exploring Kubernetes at scale in enterprise environments.</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - September, 2024</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2024-09-10/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2024-09-10/index.html</guid><description>From Kubernetes security to autonomous AI troubleshooting Summary Over the years, Arik’s role has evolved from core development to being deeply involved in solving various Kubernetes challenges. Whether it’s setting up clusters, troubleshooting CRDs, or helping developers get their applications live, he’s experienced it all. Recognising these challenges as common pain points for many in the cloud-native space, Arik set out to build tools that ease these frustrations and streamline the workflow for core developers.</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - September, 2023</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2023-09-29/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2023-09-29/index.html</guid><description>An Introduction to Kubeflow, the MLOps Platform on Kubernetes Summary Kubeflow is an open source, community-driven project for deploying and managing a cloud native machine learning stack on Kubernetes. Kubeflow has been around since 2017 and was recently accepted into CNCF as an Incubating project. At Melio AI, we have been deploying and supporting Kubeflow for the past 3 years. It’s our go-to stack for customers that want to run machine learning workloads in a private cloud or an on-premise set up.</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - July, 2023</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2023-07-26/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2023-07-26/index.html</guid><description>Optimizing Network Costs in Kubernetes Summary Nobody likes the idea of degraded performance or unscheduled downtime in their services. In many cases, the implications can be quite damaging, to say the least.
In the context of Kubernetes, many would argue that it goes against “the promise” that it’s meant to provide a container orchestration solution. That’s why teams build fault tolerance and resilience mechanisms to mitigate the risks of such issues in their environments. However, the solutions to these challenges aren’t always straightforward.</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - May, 2023</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2023-05-24/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2023-05-24/index.html</guid><description>Synthetic Testing with Canary Checker Summary Canary Checker https://github.com/flanksource/canary-checker is an open-source, Kubernetes native health check framework that supports 3 different types of checks:
Active Application health checks involve sending periodic requests to the service or application and checking the response to ensure that it is working correctly, Active health checks are proactive and can detect issues quickly, but they can also introduce some load on the system being monitored. Active Infrastructure health checks are similar to application health checks, but instead of sending a request to the application it sends a request to the infrastructure to deploy a new application or infrastructure component e.g. a new Kubernetes pod or EC2 instance. Passive health checks rely on monitoring the activity in the system, analyzing it, and detecting anomalies or errors. Passive health checks are less intrusive than active health checks, but they may not detect issues as quickly. Canary Checker supports many different protocols including:</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - August, 2022</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2022-08-25/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2022-08-25/index.html</guid><description>Scaling Kubernetes with Karpenter: Advanced Scheduling with Pod Affinity Summary For our August meetup, we invited Lukonde Mwila to come talk to us about Scaling Kubernetes with Karpenter: Advanced Scheduling with Pod Affinity &amp; Volume Topology Awareness.
One feature that draws people to Kubernetes is its ability to scale automatically. Auto-scaling Kubernetes is an essential part of your cloud-native strategy. In addition, you may be dealing with use cases requiring advanced Kubernetes scheduling requirements like pod affinity, pod anti-affinity, and volume topology awareness.</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - June, 2022</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2022-06-29/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2022-06-29/index.html</guid><description>Cloud-native machine learning: Kubeflow success stories Summary For our June meet-up, we have scheduled a panel discussion to talk about Kubeflow: The Machine Learning Toolkit for Kubernetes. We invited cloud-native specialist Harry Lee, machine learning manager Axel Tidemann and techie-turned-CEO Marko Salic to chat about their Kubeflow success story.
Gartner estimated that 85% of companies manage their hybrid and multi-cloud ML environments with cloud-native technologies (Kubernetes). Cloud-native is the de facto for AI-native companies, but it can be difficult to select the best-of-breed tools for your organisation.</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - May, 2022</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2022-05-25/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2022-05-25/index.html</guid><description>External Secrets Operator: A Cloud Native way to manage your secrets Summary For our May meetup, we invited Charl Klein to come talk to us about External Secrets Operator, a Kubernetes operator that integrates external secrets management systems with Kubernetes Secrets.
Managing secrets in Kubernetes can be a cumbersome job. How do you store and rotate your credentials currently in your project?
With External Secrets Operator (ESO for short) we leverage multi-featured solutions like AWS Secret Manager, Azure Key Vault and Hashicorp Vault to manage your sensitive data declaratively and securely. You end up with native Kubernetes secrets in your cluster, synchronized continuously with your external provider.</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - July, 2021</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2021-07-28/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2021-07-28/index.html</guid><description>Transforming into a zero-bug super developer on Kubernetes Summary For our July meetup, we have Lepolesa Libete coming to explore a cool Kubernetes tool: DevSpace with us.
DevSpace helps developers build applications that run on Kubernetes. It brings the deployment environment (i.e. Kubernetes) closer to developers working on the application. This empowers developers to collaborate and discover issues early during development.
DevSpace lets you start the entire deployment workflow with a single command. This allows for seamless redeployment of development changes. DevSpace aims to unify your deployment workflow within Kubernetes, and it is packed with built-in automation for repetitive tasks (such as docker image building and deployment). [Technicality rating: 2/4]</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - April, 2021</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2021-04-14/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2021-04-14/index.html</guid><description>How to think Cloud Native for your next Data project? Summary We invited cloud-native specialist Harry Lee and data specialist Archana Arakkal to chat about how the two ecosystems are growing to serve the community. And how you, as a practitioner, can start thinking cloud-native to improve your efficiency!
Here’s is the timestamped breakdown of the items discussed:
5:10: What are some examples of data projects in public, hybrid and multi-cloud environments? 8:52: What is the difference between cloud, cloud-computing and cloud-native? 12:45: Examples of how cloud has accelerated data science projects? 17:15: If cloud is so awesome, how come not all data projects are on the cloud? 19:20: What can we learn from the software world to accelerate cloud adoption for data projects? 21:15: Anecdotes of what you can give to the data science community who really want to move into cloud but are stumbled by the various reasons 24:07: Do you see people using cloud-native technologies in data science projects? 26:15 What is the cool trend and technology that you see the data science community is adopting in the industry? 30:03 How to adopt a typical cloud-native architecture (such as microservice, declarative APIs, etc) to data science project? 32:37: How would you transition a traditional ML project to a cloud-native ML project? 36:10: When does it not make sense to adopt cloud-native approach for data science project? 40:50: What is your experience with re-architecting data science projects, and what is your anecdotal advice? (Archie) 44:40: What is your experience with re-architecting data science projects? What to do and not to do? (Harry) Questions from audiences:</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - November, 2020</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-11-25/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-11-25/index.html</guid><description>If it ain’t broke, rewrite it! - Inject innovation in restrictive environments Summary How do you rewrite code while keeping the business running? Jose Pita has taken us through his team’s cloud native journey and shared his team’s experiences in overcoming technical as well as business challenges.
In this session, Jose covered:
Standard Bank Alchemy team’s cloud native journey How to build trust and speak to business How to nurture a long lasting team culture How to build a team and not a product Session Recording References Slides (PPT)</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - September, 2020</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-09-23/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-09-23/index.html</guid><description>Using Google Anthos to unlock cloud-native hybridization awesomeness Summary Google Anthos has come a long way since its GA announcement more than a year ago. Anthos is a combination of many services under the hood - all revolving around easing the deployment of Kubernetes anywhere and everywhere.
Julian has taken us through how a hypothetical SaaS company leverages Anthos to deliver their products to their customers.
In this session, Julian covered:</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - July, 2020</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-07-29/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-07-29/index.html</guid><description>Multi-cluster Kubernetes, the easy way [with Rancher] Summary We had the pleasure of hosting Tom Otomanski at our July CNCJ meetup last week. Tom showcased how Rancher enables effortless management of multiple Kubernetes clusters through a single interface.
In this session, Tom covered:
Creating a Kubernetes cluster on AWS through Rancher Managing Kubernetes cluster with common operations through Rancher Showcased all Kubernetes configurations in the Rancher GUI Session Recording References Slides (PDF) Rancher Server Documentation Rancher Blog Kubernetes Master Class Rancher Academy Rancher Labs YouTube Rancher Users Slack</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - June, 2020</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-06-29/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-06-29/index.html</guid><description>[Kubernetes] A demo of Rancher’s RKE Summary Bradley Cloete gave us a glimpse into the power and simplicity of Rancher’s RKE. RKE’s easy Kubernetes life cycle management is a breeze for novice and experts alike. Bradley showed us how Kubernetes’ day 2 operations (cluster backup/restore/scale) can be straightforward with RKE.
Session Recording References Rancher Academy: Certified Rancher Operator: Level 1</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - May, 2020</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-05-26/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-05-26/index.html</guid><description>[Kubernetes] Embracing Failure: Lessons learned from 50 post-mortems Summary In this session, Moshe’s covered his anecdotal lessons learned on deploying Kubernetes:
⛔ Some of the most common failure modes of Kubernetes clusters ⭐ Best practices you can apply to mitigate these failure modes 👨‍💻 A live demo simulating failure and then applying policies to prevent it Session Recording Slides Google Docs: Embracing failure - Lessons learned from 50 post-mortems</description></item><item><title>CNCJ - Feb, 2020</title><link>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-02-13/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://melio.ai/events/resources/2020-02-13/index.html</guid><description>Webinar - Kubernetes Fundamentals Summary We enjoyed how Roger simplifies the complex jargons and concepts into simple analogies. The demo on local deployment of a Kubernetes cluster was easy-to-follow and comprehensive.
Here is a summary on one of the Q&amp;A’s:
❓ What is the landscape of Kubernetes in South Africa enterprise? Are they using it in production or are still hesitant? 💬 Enterprise are paying a conscious effort in developing the competency in cloud-native technologies. There are many corporates who are running Kubernetes in production already. Those who are not, have started their journey or are testing workloads on an established Kuberentes enviornment. In the next 2 years, we will see a lot more Kubernetes clusters in production. Session Recording Zoom share link</description></item></channel></rss>